One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
The Legend of the Mermaid
I'm deflating!
That was close!
Why did they fire at their own battleship?
Are they stupid?!
Anyway, I've shrunk again.
The idea of Gear Third seems so amazing and powerful,
but my body's reaction is awkward.
I stayed inflated for about a minute,
so I'll probably remain this size for another minute.
I'd better hide until I return to normal,
or I'll be killed!
I can't tell if he's serious or not,
but he's still alive.
Well, it would've been a shame if he had died in that shelling.
There's the island gate-waina!
We're almost there-waina!
Hurry!
Your dear Franky has been taken away just like Tom-san was.
Do you wanna come along?
Ribbit!
Straw Hat was raising hell on that battleship just a moment ago,
but now he's been blown to smithereens!
Serves you right! Your captain is dead!
Hey now, they fired at the ship
while their own men were on it.
This is the power of a buster call,
the attack I set in motion!
This is justice, Cutty Flam!
Now, hand Nico Robin over to us.
In return, I could make your charges go away.
Why do you have to protect
that woman in the first place?
You're not even a pirate.
Are you saying you'd trust that wicked woman—
the kin of those Ohara devils—
over the World Government that protects
you peasants every day?!
If you defy us like Tom did, you'll end up just like h-
M-My face can't get any more swollen!
He drew the elephant sword, Funkfreed!
That thing is powerful!
Listen, Funkfreed. We'll ensure they can't resist any longer...
by fatally wounding Nico Robin while her guard is down.
Take this!
Elephant Chop!
Bastard!
He stopped it!
You're hopeless through and through.
Funkfreed! You're an elephant!
You shouldn't be losing to him!
Break free and cut them to shreds!
Change your nose back to normal, elephant,
unless you want a bullet right between the eyes.
All right. That's good. You're smart.
Nico Robin, will Straw Hat
and the others come here?
They all will. I'm sure.
I thought I told you that I'm betting everything on them, Spanda.
What?
I never thought I'd see the day.
If I could have done anything back then...
I'm changing the charges.
For the crime of building a pirate ship
for Pirate King Gold Roger,
the shipwright Tom will be escorted to Enies Lobby.
That is all.
What got into that old geezer?
Oh, well. I don't have
business with his apprentices.
Release those two!
Tom-san can't be saved now.
There's nothing we can do
against the World Government.
Hang in there. Tom-san saved you two!
Make an enemy of the World Government,
and your days will be numbered!
Enies Lobby is the government's Judicial Island.
No criminals taken there...
have ever returned!
Is he mental?
What should we do?
Are you mental, too?!
Just keep going; give him what he wants.
It's none of our concern!
Y-Yes, sir.
Stop, Puffing Tom!
Where are you taking your creator?!
Ribbit, ribbit!
I won't let you pass!
Give Tom-san back!
I wanted to take back Tom-san at any cost.
Everyone knows the myth
of the impregnable Enies Lobby.
Everyone knows the power
of the World Government.
At every turn, the Straw Hats upend what we all know.
To rescue a friend,
not one of them hesitates
to declare war on the whole world.
It's exhilarating.
To this very day, I've never forgotten Tom-san's death.
The stupid face of that official...
Every time I thought of it,
I hoped that...
Hey, stop it, you idiot! Stop it! Hey!
one day I'd be able to crush him!
Just like that.
Thanks to them, my wish came true.
Weapons Left!
I've already died once before.
I'm willing to sacrifice myself to get the Straw Hats outta here alive!
Now, hand over that escort ship!
I'll prepare their escape route!
I'll fight, too. I'm okay now.
Run with all your might!
You'll die if you stay on the island!
Sail out on my raft!
And you, Saul?
This is it for me. He got me.
Go!
I don't want to! I'd be alone at sea!
This is different from back on Ohara.
I have nothing to fear;
I'm not alone anymore!
H-He found me!
You've sure got some unbalanced combat skills.
You oughta embrace that.
I mean, it's the price you pay
for the power you used earlier.
Vital Response: Paper Art Fighting Form.
Finger Pistol!
After all, your ridiculous attacks wouldn't...
I-I'm stuck!
This is bad!
It's a shame, but you're gonna die in that goofy form, Straw Hat!
Finger Pistol: Spots!
Go back to normal, body!
Hurry! Hurry! I'm gonna be killed!
The damage I took earlier is affecting my legs!
Oh? My body's coming back!
I'm returning to normal!
See? My attacks...
did do a number on you.
Is there anything we can do?
We have to do something! We'll all drown!
We still haven't even gotten Robin-chan back yet!
Is this it? My life...
was quite fun.
Hey! I haven't lived long enough!
Besides, Usopp, proud warrior of the sea,
shouldn't end up drowning!
I can't hold my breath any longer!
I can't breathe! Everything's going dark!
Help!
You'll be fine. Stay with me.
I won't let you die!
What?! What's going on?!
Something's pulling me!
Oh, am I dreaming?
I must be!
Several sailors are drowning at sea.
An elegant tail fin appears in their fading consciousness.
They look up and see long hair flowing in the water.
She's lovely.
The legend of the mermaid appears as a vision.
If I'm dreaming, I don't want to...
wake up!
We're taking the express! Now hold your breath, guys!
It's...
– It's...
It's... a dugong?!
Sorry, marines! We're gonna
use this ship to escape.
Well, we're done cleaning up the escort ship,
or should I say, our exit strategy!
Indeed.
All we have to do now is wait
for Straw Hat and the others.
What's that?
Don't...
die!
Hurry!
The main gate to Enies Lobby
is just ahead!
We're almost there!
Go, giants!
Leave it to us!
We can leave the island-waina!
We can escape-waina!
All right!
There, we did it!
Are you impressed with the guts of us giants?!
What?!
Oh, no!
Three battleships!
They beat us here!
Look! They actually made it!
I'm sure we left them tied up in the courthouse!
How did they escape?
Vice Admiral!
Yeah...
– Secure the targets.
– Yes, sir!
State your unit, department, and marine code,
show your ID badge, and get aboard this ship!
Okay. Go ahead.
What a relief. I thought we were gonna
go down with the island.
Resistance is futile, pirates.
Make one move, and we'll open fire.
This is bad!
It sure doesn't seem like
they're gonna let us go.
The harbor and the fiery island are behind us.
There's no place to escape-waina.
Guns and cannons are in front of us.
What're you thinking about right now, Paulie?
Memories of my life.
That's not a good sign.
And...
And?
The hell that lies before us.
Ribbit!
We've recovered the marines and officials.
All ships, stand clear of the main gate.
What're they gonna do?!
Battleships 6, 7, and 8 identified
pirates in front of the main gate.
Hey, you guys! Wake up!
Hey!
It's a miracle.
How weird. They must've experienced a terrible shock.
They all stopped breathing,
so they didn't swallow much water.
Good thing they're all okay. That said,
what in the world is shocking enough to make them stop breathing?
It was you.
Hm?
You must be the friend that
pirate king kid came to rescue.
I saw you at Shift Station, right? I remember.
Back then,
I never thought you guys
would pull something like this.
Put some clothes on, you damn hag!
I laughed when I heard him say
he was gonna be king of the pirates,
Our friends are waiting!
Don't stand in our way!
but who knows? It might actually happen.
Is Nami-san okay?
You guys are as hardy as ever.
I'm glad you're alive!
Ahhh! It was real!
Mermaids don't exist!
So the tales were true
about people seeing a mermaid...
then realizing it was just a dugong!
You morons! She still hasn't
said she's a mermaid!
Don't give up on the dream yet!
I'm an icefish mermaid.
Stop it! Don't say "icefish"!
But I've never heard of a mermaid with legs.
I have an objection, too!
Mermaids should be more...
When mermaids are around 30,
our tail fins split in two,
and we become able to live on land. We're a mysterious species.
If you go to Fishman Island someday, you'll see.
Hm? They split in two? Oh, I see!
They say when a cat lives 100 years, its tail
splits in two, and it becomes a monster.
Oh, a feline abomination, huh?!
Don't lump me in with monsters!
Couldn't you at least say
thank you for what I did?!
Thank you very much, Kokoro-san!
No problem.
Robin-chwaaan!
Huh? Where am I?
Robin!
I'm so glad we made it in time,
Robin! You're safe!
Robin!
Yes, all thanks to you guys.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it!
Grandma! That's amazing!
So you were a mermaid all this time?!
I thought you were different
since you have fins and scales!
Pay attention! You're her grandkid!
Chopper?!
Are you okay?
Huh?
I can't move my body.
I'm not surprised. We'll tell you what
happened when this is all over.
Zoro!
Zoro! I mean, Zoro-kun!
Hey, look at that.
It's hard to believe that's the island
we were on until just a bit ago.
What's with this attack?
It's already a sea of flames!
I heard that their orders are not
to kill Nico Robin with the shelling.
So that's why they're not targeting this bridge?
Trying not to kill her must mean
they still intend to get her back.
Once they're through with Enies Lobby,
they'll probably come after us to recapture Nico Robin.
H-Hey, isn't that bad?
We're all already battered and bruised,
and there's a ton of crazy powerful
guys on those battleships, right?
Where's Luffy right now?
Dust from their fighting still rises from the top of this bridge's first pillar.
His opponent is, naturally,
that pigeon guy, Rob Lucci.
It's not far from here! If we give him a hand...
Don't bother.
The pigeon guy is no ordinary man.
We wouldn't want to get dragged
into the fight and get separated again.
We have to make sure we still have an escape route...
whenever that line of battleships turns this way.
We'll wait for Luffy right here.
That's all we need to do.
The storm is just beginning.
Understood.
Franky, your men...
Don't be stupid!
They've got the luck of the devil!
They're fine. I'm sure they've gotten away safely!
Hey, Paulie! Come back!
What're you gonna do with that transponder snail?!
I'm gonna find out how the Straw Hats are doing!
Dammit! It's cannon fire!
Big Bro!
This is the last time!
I won't stop until I take you down.
Are you gonna exhaust yourself and die?
I don't know the future.
Gear Second!